

#### **INFO**



Taariq Zubair Langenhoven



081 231 9320



taariqlangenhoven@



7 Zann Street, Witzenville, TULBAGH, 6820



taariq57

### TOOLS AND TECHNOLOGIES

- Windows XP, 7, 8, 10, 11
- Windows Server 2012
- Microsoft Office 2010 2019
- Microsoft Office 365
- MS Teams
- MS Outlook
- WKOD Cemis
- Atom
- Sublime Text
- Visual Studio

### CURRICULUM VITAE OF TAARIQ LANGENHOVEN

#### **ABOUT ME**



I am a highly motivated person applying for the position of Trainee Web Administrator. Throughout my education, I have demonstrated high levels of motivation and work ethic. I am an honest, reliable and hard-working person. I am confident that my experience/skills will be an asset to your organization, I know that it will allow me to make major contributions to the workplace.

#### **EDUCATION**



#### 2016

NATIONAL SENIOR CERTIFICATE: TULBAGH HIGH

#### 2017

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY AND COMPUTER SCIENCE NCV LEVEL 2:

STELLENBOSCH BOLAND COLLEGE

I achieved above 75% for my Office Data Processing L2, Electronics and Introduction to Systems Development practical's.

#### 2018

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY AND COMPUTER SCIENCE NCV LEVEL 3:

STELLENBOSCH BOLAND COLLEGE

I achieved above 80% for my Office Data Processing L3, Computer Hardware and Software and Principles of Computer Programming practical's.

#### 2019

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY AND COMPUTER SCIENCE NCV LEVEL 4:

STELLENBOSCH BOLAND COLLEGE

I achieved above 80% for my Office Data Processing L4, Data Communication and Networking and Computer Programming practical's.



# CURRICULUM VITAE OF TAARIQ LANGENHOVEN

## MORE TOOLS AND TECHNOLOGIES

- IQ Retail
- Huru

#### **SKILLS**

- JavaScript
- HTML/HTML5
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- .Net Framework
- Visual Basic
- Driver's License code C1
- Teamwork
- Very good active listening skills
- Problem-solving
- Technical support
- Computer Repair
- Troubleshooting
- Networking
- Good communication and interpersonal skills.
- The ability to prioritise tasks.

#### **EXPERIENCE**



Nov 2017 - Jan 2018

APPRENTICE TECHNICIAN

ML-SOLUTIONS TULBAGH

I was responsible for repairing computers and updating them as well as installing surveillance cameras and setting up Wi-Fi routers for factories and homes.

#### March 2020 - July 2021

IT CHAMPION / NETWORKER ADMIN RONDEHEUWEL PRIMARY SCHOOL HERMON

I was responsible for Maintaining and operating information technology procedures and systems of the school in co-operation with the principal, the senior management team, the teachers and the governing body.

Mainly my job required me to look after the school's computer lab, where I occasionally had to repair computers. I was also in charge of maintaining the school's server.

I also had the opportunity to give Computer practice lessons to the learners.



# CURRICULUM VITAE OF TAARIQ LANGENHOVEN

#### **MORE SKILLS**

- Documenting and recording information
- Collecting data and information.
- Accuracy and attention to detail
- Calm under pressure
- File management

#### Nov 2021 - Nov 2022

IT CHAMPION / ADMIN OFFICER STEINTHAL SCHOOL OF SKILLS TULBAGH

I was responsible for Maintaining and operating information technology procedures and systems of the school.

My job mainly required me to make data capturing of the school's learners easier for example by creating excel/word documents that automatically adds up the absent learners or documents that automatically adds up the learner's total marks for the Term/Year

The job also required me to maintain the computer lab and on occasion I repaired the schools' computers.

Jan 2023 – Apr 2023 (Seasonal) WEIGHBRIDGE DATA CAPTURER RHODES FOOD GROUP TULBAGH

I was responsible for capturing and recording trips of raw product, empty bins and equipment to and from depots and cold stores while ensuring that the movement of raw product and utilities are carried out timeously.

My job also required me to liaise with cold store supervisors and with the depo supervisor regarding transport needs. I had to ensure that the relevant documentation was completed correctly and accurately as well as reviewing transport reports printout to verify correct trip charges.

Another part of my job entails maintaining paper and electronic files.



#### Aug 2023 - October 2023

COUNTER SALES REPRENTATIVE

POSTNET CERES

**CERES** 

I was responsible for greeting customers, answering to inquiries, keeping the counter clean and organized, taking phone calls, managing inventories, collecting payments, stocking shelves, performing bookkeeping activities, and informing customers on special offers.

My job also required me to make printouts on customer demand where we used printers such as Large Format inkjet printers, thermal printers and laser printers.

#### **REFERENCES**



#### Leon van Schalkwyk

LECTURER AT BOLAND COLLEGE

**Tel**: 074 188 2185

Email: <a href="mailto:leonvs@bolandcollege.com">leonvs@bolandcollege.com</a>

#### **Andretti Dawson**

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SPECIALIST AT ML-

SOLUTIONS **Tel**: 071 871 4707

Email: andrettidawson@gmail.com

#### **Winston Forbes**

PRINCIPAL AT RONDEHEUWEL PRIMARY SCHOOL

Tel: 079 333 9898

Email: wforbes81@gmail.com

#### Wilmar Saville

HEAD OF IT DEPARTMENT AT STEINTHAL SCHOOL

OF SKILLS

**Tel**: 084 704 7876

Email: wilmars@telkomsa.net

#### Mario Demas

DEPARTMENT MANAGER AT RHODES FOOD GROUP

**Tel**: 079 159 8650

Email: mario.demas@rfg.com

#### **Chante Pienaar**

STORE MANAGER AT POSTNET CERES

Tel: 066 229 2627

Email: n/a